<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReproductorMusica</string>
    <string-array name="songs">
        <item>Up with it girl
    Rock with it girl
    Show dem it girl (bada bang bang)
    Bounce with it girl
    Dance with it girl
    Get with it girl (bada bang bang)

    Come on, come on, turn the radio on
    It\'s friday night and I won\'t be long
    Gotta do my hair,
    I put my make up on
    It\'s friday night and I won\'t be long

    Til I hit the dance floor (bada bang)
    Hit the dance floor (bada bang)
    I got all I need (sia)
    No I ain\'t got cash
    No I ain\'t got cash
    But I got you baby
    (just you and me)

    Baby I don\'t need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    Baby I don\'t need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    But I don\'t need no money
    You worth more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I can feel the beat
    Mek di beat jus tek control
    I don\'t need no money
    You\'re more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I keep dancing
    Free up yourself, get outa control

    Come on, come on, turn the radio on
    It\'s saturday and I won\'t be long
    Gotta paint my nails, put my high heels on
    It\'s saturday and I won\'t be long

    Til I hit the dance floor (bada bang)
    Hit the dance floor (bada bang)
    I got all I need (sia)
    No I ain\'t got cash
    No I ain\'t got cash
    But I got you baby
    (just you and me)

    Baby I don\'t need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    Baby I don\'t need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    But I don\'t need no money
    You worth more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I can feel the beat
    Mek di beat jus tek control
    I don't need no money
    You're more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I keep dancing
    Free up yourself, get outa control

    Me and you girl, you and me
    Drop it to di floor an mek
    Mi see your energy because
    Mi nah play na hide an seek
    Wah fi see di ting you have
    Weg mek me feel weak girl
    Cause anytime you wine and kotch it
    Di selector pull it up an pull
    It pon repeat girl
    I'm nah touch a dollar in my pocket
    Cause nuttin in this world
    Ain't more dan what you worth

    But I don't need no money
    You worth more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I can feel the beat
    Mek di beat jus tek control
    I don't need no money
    You worth more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I keep dancing
    Free up yourself, get outa control
    Oh, oh

    Baby I don't need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    Baby I don't need dollar bills
    To have fun tonight
    (I love cheap thrills)
    But I don't need no money
    You worth more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I can feel the beat
    Mek di beat jus tek control
    I don't need no money
    You're more than diamonds, more than gold
    As long as I keep dancing
    Free up yourself, get outa control

    La, la, la, la, la, la
    (I love cheap thrills)
    La, la, la, la, la, la
    (I love cheap thrills)
    La, la, la, la, la, la
    (I love cheap thrills)
    La, la, la, la, la, la
    (I love cheap thrills)
</item>
<item>
    Here come old flat-top, he come grooving slowly
He got ju-ju eyeballs, he\'s one holy roller
He got hair down to his knees
Got to be a joker, he just do what he please
He wear no shoeshine, he\'s got toe-jam football
He got monkey finger, he shoot Coca-Cola
He say, "I know you, you know me"
One thing I can tell you is you got to be free
Come together, right now
Over me
He roller-coaster, he got early warning
He got muddy water, he one mojo filter
He say, "One and one and one is three"
Got to be good looking 'cause he\'s so hard to see
Come together, right now
Over me
Come together, right now
Come together, right now
Come together, right now
Over me
</item>
        <item>
            I did my best to notice
When the call came down the line
Up to the platform of surrender
I was brought but I was kind
And sometimes I get nervous
When I see an open door
Close your eyes, clear your heart
Cut the cord

Are we human or are we dancer?
My sign is vital, my hands are cold
And I\'m on my knees
Looking for the answer
Are we human or are we dancer?

Pay my respects to grace and virtue
Send my condolences to good
Give my regards to soul and romance
They always did the best they could
And so long to devotion
You taught me everything I know
Wave goodbye, wish me well
You\'ve got to let me go

Are we human or are we dancer?
My sign is vital, my hands are cold
And I'm on my knees
Looking for the answer
Are we human or are we dancer?

Will your system be alright
When you dream of home tonight?
There is no message we\'re receiving
Let me know, is your heart still beating?

Are we human or are we dancer?
My sign is vital, my hands are cold
And I\'m on my knees
Looking for the answer
Are we human or are we dancer?

Are we human or are we dancer?
Are we human or are we dancer?
        </item>
        <item>
            You are beautiful on the inside
You are innocence personified
And I will drag you down and sell you out
Run away
I am cold like December snow
I have carved out this soul made of stone
And I will drag you down and sell you out
Embraced by the darkness, I\'m losing the light
Encircled by demons, I fight
What have I become, now that I\'ve betrayed
Everyone I\'ve ever loved, I pushed them all away
And I have been a slave to the Judas in my mind
Is there something left for me to save
In the wreckage of my life, my life
I\'m becom-, I\'m becom-, I\'m becoming
I\'m becom-, I\'m becom-, I\'m becoming
Judas in, Judas in my mind
I\'m becom-, I\'m becom-, I\'m becoming
I\'m becom-, I\'m becom-, I\'m becoming
Judas in, Judas in my mind
Judas in my mind
Oh, this…
        </item>
        <item>
            Here we are
And I can\'t think from all the pills, hey
Start the car and take me home
Here we are
And your too drunk to hear a word I say
Start the car and take me home
Just tonight I will stay and well throw it all away
When the light hits your eyes
Its telling me I\'m right
And if I, I am through
Then its all because of you
Just tonight
Here I am
And I can\'t seem to see straight
But I'm too numb to feel right now
And here I am
Watching the clock that\'s ticking away my time
I\'m too numb to feel right now
Just tonight I will stay and well throw it all away
When the light hits your eyes
Its telling me I\'m right
And if I, I am through
Then its all because of you
Just tonight
Do you understand who I am do you wanna know
Can you really see through me
Now I…
        </item>
        <item>
            On a cobweb afternoon
In a room full of emptiness
By a freeway I confess
I was lost in the pages
Of a book full of death
Reading how we\'ll die alone
And if we\'re good, we\'ll lay to rest
Anywhere we want to go
In your house I long to be
Room by room patiently
I\'ll wait for you there
Like a stone
I\'ll wait for you there
Alone
On my deathbed I will pray
To the gods and the angels
Like a pagan to anyone
Who will take me to heaven
To a place I recall
I was there so long ago
The sky was bruised
The wine was bled
And there you led me on
In your house I long to be
Room by room patiently
I\'ll wait for you there
Like a stone
I\'ll wait for you there
Alone
Alone
And on…
        </item>
        <item>
            One, two, one, two, three
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah, uh!
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah, uh!
Never had much faith in love or miracles (miracles) uh!
Never wanna put my heart on the line, uh!
But swimming in your water is something spiritual (spiritual) uh!
I\'m born again every time you spend the night, uh!
\'Cause your sex takes me to paradise
Yeah your sex takes me to paradise
And it shows, yeah, yeah, yeah
\'Cause you make me feel like, I\'ve been locked out of heaven
For too long, for too long
Yeah you make me feel like, I\'ve been locked out of heaven
For too long, for too long
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah, uh!
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah, uh!
You bring me to my knees
You make me testify, uh!
You can make a sinner change his ways, uh!
Open up…
        </item>
        <item>
            Coming out of my cage
And I\'ve been doing just fine
Gotta gotta be down
Because I want it all
It started out with a kiss
How did it end up like this
It was only a kiss, it was only a kiss
Now I\'m falling asleep
And she\'s calling a cab
While he\'s having a smoke
And she\'s taking a drag
Now they\'re going to bed
And my stomach is sick
And it\'s all in my head
But she\'s touching his chest
Now, he takes off her dress
Now, letting me go
I just can\'t look its killing me
And taking control
Jealousy, turning saints into the sea
Swimming through sick lullabies
Choking on your alibis
But it\'s just the price I pay
Destiny is calling me
Open up my eager eyes
Cause I\'m Mr Brightside
I\'m coming out of my cage
And I\'ve been doing just fine
Gotta gotta be down
Because I want it all
It…
        </item>
        <item>
        Nightmare! (Now your nightmare comes to life)
Dragged ya down below
Down to the devil\'s show
To be his guest forever
Peace of mind is less than never
Hate to twist your mind
But God ain\'t on your side
An old acquaintance severed
Burn the world your last endeavor
Flesh is burning
You can smell it in the air
\'Cause men like you have
Such easy soul to steal (steal)
So stand in line while
They ink numbers in your head
You\'re now a slave
Until the end of time here
Nothing stops the madness,
Turning, haunting, yearning
Pull the trigger
You should have known
The price of evil
And it hurts to know
That you belong here, yeah
Ooh, it\'s your fuckin\' nightmare
Can\'t wake up in a sweat
\'Cause it ain\'t over yet
Still dancing with your demons
Victim of your own creation
Beyond the will to fight
Where all that\'s wrong is right
Where hate don\'t need a reason
Loathing self-assassination
You\'ve been lied to
Just to rape you of your site
And now they have the nerve
To tell you how to feel (feel)
So sedated as they
Medicate your brain
And while you slowly
Go insane they tell ya
Given with the best intentions
Help you with your complications
You should have known
The price of evil
And it hurts to know
That you belong here, yeah
No one to call
Everybody to fear
Your tragic fate is looking so clear, yeah
Oh, it\'s your fuckin' nightmare
Fight
Not to fail
Not to fall
Or you\'ll end up like the others
Die
Die again
Drenched in sin
With no respect for another
Down
Feel the fire (fire)
Feel the hate
Your pain is what we desire
Lost
Hit the wall (wall)
Watch you crawl (crawl)
Such a replaceable liar
And I know you hear their voices (calling from above)
And I know they may seem real (these signals of love)
But our life\'s made up of choices (some without appeal)
They took for granted your soul
And it\'s ours now to steal
You should have known
The price of evil
And it hurts to know
That you belong here, yeah
No one to call
Everybody to fear
Your tragic fate is looking so clear, yeah
Ooh, it\'s your fuckin\' nightmare
        </item>
        <item>
            I\'m tired of being what you want me to be
Feeling so faithless, lost under the surface
I don\'t know what you're expecting of me
Put under the pressure of walking in your shoes
Caught in the undertow, just caught in the undertow
Every step that I take is another mistake to you
Caught in the undertow, just caught in the undertow
I\'ve become so numb, I can\'t feel you there
Become so tired, so much more aware
By becoming this all I want to do
Is be more like me and be less like you
Can\'t you see that you\'re smothering me?
Holding too tightly, afraid to lose control
\'Cause everything that you thought I would be
Has fallen apart right in front of you
Caught in the undertow, just caught in the undertow
Every step that I take is another mistake to you
Caught in…
        </item>
        <item>
            Look, I was gonna go easy on you and not to hurt your feelings
But I\'m only going to get this one chance
Something\'s wrong, I can feel it (Six minutes, Slim Shady, you\'re on)
Just a feeling I've got, like something\'s about to happen, but I don't know what
If that means, what I think it means, we\'re in trouble, big trouble,
And if he is as bananas as you say, I\'m not taking any chances
You were just what the doctor ordered
I\'m beginning to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
Now who thinks their arms are long enough to slap box, slap box?
They said I rap like a robot, so call me Rapbot
But for me to rap like a computer must be in my genes
I got a laptop in my back pocket
My pen\'ll go off when I half-cock it
Got a fat knot from that rap profit
Made a living and a killing off it
Ever since Bill Clinton was still in office
With Monica Lewinsky feeling on his nut-sack
I\'m an MC still as honest
But as rude and indecent as all hell syllables, killaholic (Kill \'em all with)
This slickety, gibbedy, hibbedy hip hop
You don\'t really wanna get into a pissing match with this rappidy rap
Packing a Mac in the back of the Ac, pack backpack rap, yep, yackidy-yac
The exact same time I attempt these lyrical acrobat stunts while I\'m practicing
That I\'ll still be able to break a motherfuckin\' table
Over the back of a couple of faggots and crack it in half
Only realized it was ironic I was signed to Aftermath after the fact
How could I not blow? All I do is drop F-bombs, feel my wrath of attack
Rappers are having a rough time period, here\'s a Maxipad
It\'s actually disastrously bad
For the wack while I'm masterfully constructing this masterpiece as
I\'m beginning to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
Now who thinks their arms are long enough to slap box, slap box?
Let me show you maintaining this shit ain\'t that hard, that hard
Everybody want the key and the secret to rap immortality like I have got
Well, to be truthful the blueprint's simply rage and youthful exuberance
Everybody loves to root for a nuisance
Hit the earth like an asteroid, did nothing but shoot for the moon since
MC\'s get taken to school with this music
\'Cause I use it as a vehicle to bust a rhyme
Now I lead a new school full of students
Me? I'm a product of Rakim, Lakim Shabazz, 2Pac N-
-W.A, Cube, hey, Doc, Ren, Yella, Eazy, thank you, they got Slim
Inspired enough to one day grow up, blow up and be in a position
To meet Run DMC and induct them into the motherfuckin\' Rock n\'
Roll Hall of Fame
Even though I walk in the church and burst in a ball of flames
Only Hall of Fame I be inducted in is the alcohol of fame
On the wall of shame
You fags think it\'s all a game \'til I walk a flock of flames
Off of planking, tell me what in the fuck are you thinking?
Little gay looking boy
So gay I can barely say it with a straight face looking boy
You witnessing a massacre
Like you watching a church gathering take place looking boy
Oy vey, that boy\'s gay, that's all they say looking boy
You get a thumbs up, pat on the back
And a way to go from your label everyday looking boy
Hey, looking boy, what you say looking boy?
I got a hell yeah from Dre looking boy
I\'mma work for everything I have
Never ask nobody for shit, get outta my face looking boy
Basically boy you\'re never gonna be capable
To keep up with the same pace looking boy
\'Cause I'm beginning to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
The way I\'m racing around the track, call me Nascar, Nascar
Dale Earnhardt of the trailer park, the White Trash God
Kneel before General Zod this planet's Krypton, no Asgard, Asgard
So you be Thor and I'll be Odin, you rodent, I\'m omnipotent
Let off then I'm reloading immediately with these bombs I\'m totin'
And I should not be woken
I\'m the walking dead, but I'm just a talking head, a zombie floating
But I got your mom deep throating
I\'m out my ramen noodle, we have nothing in common, poodle
I\'m a doberman, pinch yourself in the arm and pay homage, pupil
It\'s me, my honesty's brutal
But it\'s honestly futile if I don't utilize what I do though
For good at least once in a while
So I wanna make sure somewhere in this chicken scratch I scribble and doodle
Enough rhymes to maybe to try and help get some people through tough times
But I gotta keep a few punchlines just in case cause even you unsigned
Rappers are hungry looking at me like it\'s lunchtime
I know there was a time where once I
Was king of the underground, but I still rap like I'm on my Pharoahe Monch grind
So I crunch rhymes, but sometimes when you combine
Appeal with the skin color of mine
You get too big and here they come trying to,
Censor you like that one line I said on I\'m Back from the Marshall Mathers LP
One where I tried to say I take seven kids from Columbine
Put \'em all in a line, add an AK-47, a revolver and a nine
See if I get away with it now that I ain\'t as big as I was, but I've
Morphed into an immortal coming through the portal
You\'re stuck in a time warp from 2004 though
And I don't know what the fuck that you rhyme for
You\'re pointless as Rapunzel with fucking cornrows
You\'re like normal, fuck being normal
And I just bought a new Raygun from the future
To just come and shoot ya like when Fabolous made Ray J mad
\'Cause Fab said he looked like a fag at Maywhether’s pad
Singin\' to a man while they played piano
Man, oh man, that was a 24/7 special on the cable channel
So Ray J went straight to the radio station the very next day
Hey, Fab, I\'mma kill you
Lyrics coming at you at supersonic speed, (JJ Fad)
Uh, sama lamaa duma lamaa you assuming I\'m a human
What I gotta do to get it through to you I\'m superhuman
Innovative and I\'m made of rubber
So that anything you saying ricocheting off of me and it\'ll glue to you
I\'m never stating, more than never demonstrating
How to give a motherfuckin' audience a feeling like it\'s levitating
Never fading, and I know that the haters are forever waiting
For the day that they can say I fell off, they\'d be celebrating
Cause I know the way to get \'em motivated
I make elevating music, you make elevator music
Oh, he\'s too mainstream
Well, that\'s what they do when they get jealous, they confuse it
It\'s not hip hop, it\'s pop, cause I found a hella way to fuse it
With rock, shock rap with Doc
Throw on Lose Yourself and make 'em lose it
I don\'t know how to make songs like that
I don\'t know what words to use
Let me know when it occurs to you
While I\'m ripping any one of these verses diverse as you
It\'s curtains, I\'m inadvertently hurtin\' you
How many verses I gotta murder to,
Prove that if you\'re half as nice at songs you can sacrifice virgins too uh!
School flunkie, pill junky
But look at the accolades the skills brung me
Full of myself, but still hungry
I bully myself cause I make me do what I put my mind to
And I\'m a million leagues above you, ill when I speak in tongues
But it\'s still tongue in cheek, fuck you
I'm drunk so Satan take the fucking wheel, I\'m asleep in the front seat
Bumping Heavy D and the Boys, still chunky, but funky
But in my head there\'s something I can feel tugging and struggling
Angels fight with devils, here\'s what they want from me
They asking me to eliminate some of the women hate
But if you take into consideration the bitter hatred that I had
Then you may be a little patient and more sympathetic to the situation
And understand the discrimination
But fuck it, life's handing you lemons, make lemonade then
But if I can\'t batter the women how the fuck am I supposed to bake them a cake then?
Don\'t mistake it for Satan
It\'s a fatal mistake if you think I need to be overseas
And take a vacation to trip a broad
And make her fall on her face and don\'t be a retard
Be a king? Think not, why be a king when you can be a God?
        </item>
        <item>
            I was scared of dentists and the dark
I was scared of pretty girls and starting conversations
Oh, all my friends are turning green
You\'re the magician\'s assistant in their dreams
Oh
Oh and they come unstuck
Lady, running down to the riptide
Taken away to the dark side
I wanna be your left hand man
I love you when you're singing that song and
I got a lump in my throat 'cause
You\'re gonna sing the words wrong
Is this movie that I think you'll like
This guy decides to quit his job and heads to New York City
This cowboy's running from himself
And she\'s been living on the highest shelf
Oh
Oh and they come unstuck
Lady, running down to the riptide
Taken away to the dark side
I wanna be your left hand man
I love you when you're singing that song and
I got…
        </item>
        <item>
            I\'ve been a liar, been a thief
Been a lover, been a cheat
All my sins need holy water, feel it washing over me
Well, little one, I don\'t want to admit to something
If all it\'s gonna cause is pain
Truth and my lies right now are falling like the rain
So let the river run
He\'s coming home with his next grasp to catch flack
Sweat jackets and dress slacks, mismatched
On his breath\'s Jack, he\'s a sex addict
And she just wants to exact revenge and get back
It\'s a chest match, she's on his back like a jet-pack
She\'s kept track of all his internet chats
And guess who just happens to be moving on to the next
Actually, just shit on my last chick and she has what my ex lacks
\'Cause she loves danger, psychopath
And you don\'t fuck with no man\'s girl, even I know that
But she devised some plan to stab him in the back
Knife in hand, says the relationship hanging by a strand
So she\'s been on the web lately
Says maybe she\'ll be my Gwen Stacy, to Spiderman
And I know she\'s using me to try to play him, I don\'t care
Hi Suzanne, but I shoulda\' said "Bye Suzanne" after the first night, but tonight I am
I\'ve been a liar, been a thief
Been a lover, been a cheat
All my sins need holy water, feel it washing over me
Well, little one, I don\'t want to admit to something
If all it\'s gonna cause is pain
Truth and my lies right now are falling like the rain
So let the river run
One-night stand turned a two-night stand
It was come sunlight, scram
Now we hug tight and
He found out, now she feels deserted and used
\'Cause he left, so what? He did it first to her, too
Now how am I supposed to tell this girl that we\'re through?
It\'s hard to find the words, I\'m aloof, nervous and Sue
Don\'t want this to hurt, but what you deserve is the truth
Don\'t take it personal, I just can\'t say this in person to you
So I revert to the studio, like hole-in-the-wall diners
Don\'t have to be reserved in a booth
I just feel like the person who I\'m turnin\' into's
Irreversible, I preyed on you like a church at the pew
And now that I got you, I don\'t want you
Took advantage of my thirst to pursue
Why do I do this dirt that I do?
Get on my soapbox and breach, my sermon and speech
Detergent and bleach is burnin\' the wound
\'Cause now with her in the womb
We can't bring her in this world, shoulda knew
To use protection \'fore I bit into your forbidden fruit, fuck
I\'ve been a liar, been a thief
Been a lover, been a cheat
All my sins need holy water, feel it washing over me
Well, little one, I don\'t want to admit to something
If all it\'s gonna cause is pain
Truth and my lies now are falling like the rain
So let the river run
My name\'s (ooh)
My name\'s (ooh)
River (ooh), river run
Call me (ooh)
Call me (ooh)
River (ooh)
We\'ll let the river run
Always the bridesmaid, never "The bride, hey!"
What can I say? If life was a highway
And deceit was an enclave
I\'d be swerving in five lanes
Speeds at a high rate, like I'm sliding on ice maybe
That\'s why I may have came you sideways
I can\'t keep my lies straight
But I made you terminate my baby
This love triangle left us in a wreck, tangled
What else can I say? It was fun for a while
Bet I really woulda\' loved your smile
Didn\'t really wanna abort
But fuck it, what\'s one more lie to tell our unborn child?
I\'ve been a liar, been a thief
Been a lover, been a cheat
All my sins need holy water, feel it washing over me
Well, little one, I don\'t want to admit to something (I\'m sorry, I fucked up)
If all it\'s gonna cause is pain
Truth and my lies now are falling like the rain
So let the river run
        </item>
        <item>
            The club isn\'t the best place to find a lover
So the bar is where I go
Me and my friends at the table doing shots
Drinking fast and then we talk slow
Come over and start up a conversation with just me
And trust me I\'ll give it a chance now
Take my hand, stop, put Van the Man on the jukebox
And then we start to dance, and now I\'m singing like
Girl, you know I want your love
Your love was handmade for somebody like me
Come on now, follow my lead
I may be crazy, don\'t mind me
Say, boy, let\'s not talk too much
Grab on my waist and put that body on me
Come on now, follow my lead
Come, come on now, follow my lead
I\'m in love with the shape of you
We push and pull like a magnet do
Although my heart is falling too
I\'m in love with your body
And last night you were in my room
And now my bedsheets smell like you
Every day discovering something brand new
I\'m in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I\'m in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I\'m in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I\'m in love with your body
Every day discovering something brand new
I'm in love with the shape of you
One week in we let the story begin
We\'re going out on our first date
You and me are thrifty, so go all you can eat
Fill up your bag and I fill up a plate
We talk for hours and hours about the sweet and the sour
And how your family is doing okay
Leave and get in a taxi, then kiss in the backseat
Tell the driver make the radio play, and I\'m singing like
Girl, you know I want your love
Your love was handmade for somebody like me
Come on now, follow my lead
I may be crazy, don\'t mind me
Say, boy, let\'s not talk too much
Grab on my waist and put that body on me
Come on now, follow my lead
Come, come on now, follow my lead
I\'m in love with the shape of you
We push and pull like a magnet do
Although my heart is falling too
I\'m in love with your body
And last night you were in my room
And now my bedsheets smell like you
Every day discovering something brand new
I\'m in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I\'m in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I'm in love with your body
Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I
I'm in love with your body
Every day discovering something brand new
I\'m in love with the shape of you
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
I\'m in love with the shape of you
We push and pull like a magnet do
Although my heart is falling too
I\'m in love with your body
Last night you were in my room
And now my bedsheets smell like you
Every day discovering something brand new
I\'m in love with your body
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
I\'m in love with your body
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
I\'m in love with your body
Come on, be my baby, come on
Come on, be my baby, come on
I\'m in love with your body
Every day discovering something brand new
I\'m in love with the shape of you
        </item>
        <item>
            I\'m hurting, baby, I\'m broken down
I need your loving, loving, I need it now
When I\'m without you
I\'m something weak
You got me begging
Begging, I\'m on my knees
I don\'t wanna be needing your love
I just wanna be deep in your love
And it\'s killing me when you\'re away
Ooh, baby,
\'Cause I really don\'t care where you are
I just wanna be there where you are
And I gotta get one little taste
Your sugar
Yes, please
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
I\'m right here, \'cause I need
Little love and little sympathy
Yeah you show me good loving
Make it alright
Need a little sweetness in my life
Your sugar
Yes, please
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
My broken pieces
You pick them up
Don\'t leave me hanging, hanging
Come give me some
When I\'m without ya
I\'m so insecure
You are the one thing
The one thing, I\'m living for
I don\'t wanna be needing your love
I just wanna be deep in your love
And it\'s killing me when you\'re away
Ooh, baby,
\'Cause I really don't care where you are
I just wanna be there where you are
And I gotta get one little taste
Your sugar
Yes, please
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
I\'m right here, \'cause I need
Little love and little sympathy
Yeah you show me good loving
Make it alright
Need a little sweetness in my life
Your sugar (your sugar)
Yes, please (yes, please)
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
Yeah
I want that red velvet
I want that sugar sweet
Don\'t let nobody touch it
Unless that somebody\'s me
I gotta be a man
There ain\'t no other way
\'Cause girl you\'re hotter than southern California Bay
I don\'t wanna play no games
I don\'t gotta be afraid
Don\'t give all that shy shit
No make up on, that\'s my
Sugar
Yes, please
Won\'t you come and put it down on me (down on me)
Oh, right here (right here),
\'Cause I need (I need)
Little love and little sympathy
Yeah you show me good loving
Make it alright
Need a little sweetness in my life
Your sugar (sugar)
Yes, please (yes, please)
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
Your sugar
Yes, please
Won't you come and put it down on me
I\'m right here, \'cause I need
Little love and little sympathy
Yeah you show me good loving
Make it alright
Need a little sweetness in my life
Your sugar
Yes, please
Won\'t you come and put it down on me
(Down on me, down on me)
        </item>
        <item>
            Hey, once upon a younger year
When all our shadows disappeared
The animals inside came out to play
Hey, when face to face with all our fears
Learned our lessons through the tears
Made memories we knew would never fade
One day my father he told me,
Son, don\'t let it slip away
He took me in his arms, I heard him say,
When you get older
Your wild life will live for younger days
Think of me if ever you\'re afraid.
He said, One day you\'ll leave this world behind
So live a life you will remember.
My father told me when I was just a child
These are the nights that never die
My father told me
When thunder clouds start pouring down
Light a fire they can\'t put out
Carve your name into those shinning stars
He said, Go venture far beyond the shores.
Don\'t forsake this life of yours.
I\'ll guide you home no matter where you are.
One day my father—he told me,
Son, don\'t let it slip away.
When I was just a kid I heard him say,
When you get older
Your wild life will live for younger days
Think of me if ever you\'re afraid.
He said, One day you'll leave this world behind
So live a life you will remember.
My father told me when I was just a child
These are the nights that never die
My father told me
These are the nights that never die
My father told me
        </item>
        <item>
            As I walk through the valley
Of the shadow of LA
The footsteps that were next to me
Have gone their separate ways
I\'ve seen enough now
To know that beautiful things
Don\'t always stay that way
I\'ve done enough now
To know this beautiful place
Isn\'t everything they say
I heard that evil comes disguised
Like a city of angels
I\'m walking towards the light
Baptized in the river
I\'ve seen a vision of my life
And I wanna be delivered
In the city was a sinner
I\'ve done a lot of things wrong
But I swear I\'m a believer
Like the prodigal son
I was out on my own
Now I\'m trying to find my way back home
Baptized in the river
I\'m delivered
I\'m delivered
You\'re from a small town
You\'re gonna grow up fast
Underneath these lights
Down in Hollywood on the boulevard
The dead come back to life
To the praying mother
And the worried father
Let your children go
If they come back, they\'ll come home stronger
And if they don\'t, you\'ll know...
I heard that evil comes disguised
Like a city of angels
I\'m walking towards the light
Baptized in the river (on my own)
Baptized in the river (on my own)
I wanna be delivered
(On my own)
(On my own)
Baptized in the river (on my own)
I wanna be delivered
Baptized in the river (on my own)
I wanna be delivered
Baptized in the river (on my own)
I wanna be delivered
I confess I\'m a sinner
I\'ve seen a vision of my life
And I wanna be delivered
        </item>
        <item>
            You\'re falling apart
From the inside out
With no one but yourself to blame
So face the truth or suffer and lose
All the games you play keep pushing me further away

Come back to me, come back to see
There\'s no reason why
Take the time to make everything alright

Run, we could run for miles
It\'ll take a while to bring me back to you
Run, we could run for miles
Will you walk the wire?
You know it\'s up to you

So where is your heart? (Have you lost all feeling?)
Go back to the start (Have you lost the meaning?)
Leaving behind everything you know
Well make a truce, there\'s nothing to prove
Get your head out the clouds or be washed away by the rain

Come back to me, come back to see
It\'s the same old story
Everytime you look the other way
So what\'s there left to say?

Run, we could run for miles
It\'ll take a while to bring me back to you
Run, we could run for miles
I should walk on by us
If you want the truth
You know it\'s up to you

Falling apart from the inside out
With no one but yourself to blame
So face the truth or suffer and lose
All the games you play keep pushing me further away

Come back to me, come back to see
The light beyond the shade
Everybody has their price to pay

Run, we could run for miles
It\'ll take a while to bring me back to you
You\'re running out of luck and the road is long enough
Tell me when you\'ve had enough
You know it\'s up to you (You know it\'s up to you)
If you want the truth (Well if you want the truth)
There\'s nothing left to prove
You know it\'s up to, YOU!
        </item>
        <item>
            Mm ba ba de
Um bum ba de
Um bu bu bum da de
Pressure pushing down on me
Pressing down on you no man ask for
Under pressure that brings a building down
Splits a family in two
Puts people on streets
Um ba ba be
Um ba ba be
De day da
Ee day da - that\'s okay
It\'s the terror of knowing
What the world is about
Watching some good friends
Screaming \'Let me out\'
Pray tomorrow gets me higher
Pressure on people people on streets
Day day de mm hm
Da da da ba ba
Okay
Chippin\' around - kick my brains around the floor
These are the days it never rains but it pours
Ee do ba be
Ee da ba ba ba
Um bo bo
Be lap
People on streets - ee da de da de
People on streets - ee da de da de da de da
It\'s the terror of knowing
What this world is about
Watching some good friends
Screaming \'Let me out\'
Pray tomorrow - gets me higher higher high
Pressure on people people on streets
Turned away from it all like a blind man
Sat on a fence but it don\'t work
Keep coming up with love but it\'s so slashed and torn
Why - why - why?
Love love love love love
Insanity laughs under pressure we\'re breaking
Can\'t we give ourselves one more chance
Why can\'t we give love that one more chance
Why can\'t we give love give love give love give love
Give love give love give love give love give love
\'Cause love\'s such an old fashioned word
And love dares you to care for
The people on the (People on streets) edge of the night
And loves (People on streets) dares you to change our way of
Caring about ourselves
This is our last dance
This is our last dance
This is ourselves
Under pressure
Under pressure
Pressure
        </item>
        <item>
            Show me how to lie
You\'re getting better all the time
And turning all against the one
Is an art that\'s hard to teach
Another clever word
Sets off an unsuspecting herd
And as you get back into line
A mob jumps to their feet
Now dance, fucker, dance
Man, he never had a chance
And no one even knew
It was really only you
And now you steal away
Take him out today
Nice work you did
You\'re gonna go far, kid
With a thousand lies
And a good disguise
Hit \'em right between the eyes
Hit \'em right between the eyes
When you walk away
Nothing more to say
See the lightning in your eyes
See \'em running for their lives
Slowly out of line
And drifting closer in your sights
So play it out I\'m wide awake
It\'s a scene about me
There\'s something in your way
And now someone is gonna pay
And if you can\'t get what you want
Well it\'s all because of me
Now dance, fucker, dance
Man, I never had a chance
And no one even knew
It was really only you
And now you\'ll lead the way
Show the light of day
Nice work you did
You\'re gonna go far, kid, trust, deceived!
With a thousand lies
And a good disguise
Hit \'em right between the eyes
Hit \'em right between the eyes
When you walk away
Nothing more to say
See the lightning in your eyes
See \'em running for their lives
Now dance, fucker, dance
He never had a chance
And no one even knew
It was really only you
So dance, fucker, dance
I never had a chance
It was really only you
With a thousand lies
And a good disguise
Hit \'em right between the eyes
Hit \'em right between the eyes
When you walk away
Nothing more to say
See the lightning in your eyes
See \'em running for their lives
Clever alibis, Lord of the flies
Hit \'em right between the eyes
Hit \'em right between the eyes
When you walk away
Nothing more to say
See the lightning in your eyes
See \'em running for their lives
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
